{
    "subject": "resource/Bobby_Pinson",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Bobby Pinson's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9346045851707458,
            "question": "Does Bobby Pinson live in the United States currently?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8931828141212463,
            "question": "Is Bobby Pinson originally from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8691413998603821,
            "question": "What country is Bobby Pinson's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7901238203048706,
            "question": "Is the United States considered Bobby Pinson's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7151020765304565,
            "question": "Where is Bobby Pinson from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6104221343994141,
            "question": "Where was Bobby Pinson raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5482648611068726,
            "question": "Where did Bobby Pinson grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47135409712791443,
            "question": "What is Bobby Pinson's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4492957293987274,
            "question": "What is known about Bobby Pinson's childhood location?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43015801906585693,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Bobby Pinson's home country?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bobby Pinson's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9197_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Bobby Pinson's childhood location?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9197_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bobby Pinson's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9197_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Bobby Pinson grow up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9197_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9197_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nAlthough the text mentions Bobby Pinson being from Tulsa, Oklahoma, and that he was raised in Pandhandle, Texas, it doesn't state that his hometown is the United States.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents confirms that Bobby Pinson was born in Tulsa, Oklahoma, which is in the United States. Therefore, the statement \"Bobby Pinson's hometown is United States\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states his hometown is the United States, but the text says he was born in Tulsa, Oklahoma and raised in Pandhandle, Texas.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}